

CARMELO MAMMANA

UNITY DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

I'm a very passionate software developer interested in all kind of technologies. More than ever with Videogames, AR/VR/XR and AI.
I graduated as Game Programmer with three years course and I took part in trade events like Milan Games Week and Lucca Comics and Games as a developer

HARD SKILLS

OOP 95%

UNITY 95%

C# 95%

GIT 90%

SOFT SKILLS

- Good communication
- Team Work
- Details oriented
- Ready to learn
- Problem Solving

CONTACTS

E-mail: carmelomammana8@gmail.com



WORK EXPERIENCES

Lead Software Developer C#-Unity

HetaLab Sept 2021 - Aug 2022 ->
Project acquired by Retail Italia Aug 2022

Worked on WebGL sim-building applications with Unity Engine for the fashion industry.

- Translate business requirements into technical requirements
- Planned, designed and built applications with testing and debugging.
- Worked with 3D artists and managed complex 3D scenes.
- Software Development Life Cycle
- General behaviours and optimizations
- Online Database (API, Download models and textures)
- UI/UX

Software Developer C#-Unity

UpSurgeon | March 2021 - Sept 2021 Milan, Italy

Worked on mobile AR applications (iOS- Android) with Unity Engine.

- ARFoundation
- Worked with 3D artists and managed complex 3D scenes.
- Software Development Life Cycle
- In-App purchase
- General behaviours and optimizations
- Online Stores Management (iOS & Android)
- III/IIX

.NET Developer

Avanade | 2019-2021

Florence, Italy

Worked as a programmer with AGILE method for a big client as Monte dei Paschi di Siena Bank using various technologies: .NET; Javascript; CSS; HTML; SQL; SharePoint

.NET Developer

Casalini Libri | May 2018 - Dec 2018 Florence, Italy

Worked as a programmer with various technologies like: .NET, SQL, JavaScript, HTML, CSS



EDUCATION

Event Horizon - Game Programmer

Bachelor's Degree | 2016 - 2019 Final thesis:Al with different difficult levels

Bachelor's Degree as Game Programmer. Completed three years of course in Game Programmer and concurrently working on personal projects. The course was focused on C++, C#, Unity and teamwork with Designers and Artists

ISIS Gobetti - Volta - Programmer

High School Diploma | 2009 - 2016

High School Diploma as Programmer